{
    "challenge": [
        {
            "id": "0",
            "question": "Are you ready?",
            "answer": "gobstoppers!",
            "pic": ""
        },
        {
            "id": "1",
            "question": "What is the organ that takes 20% of energy of the body?",
            "answer": "the brain",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "question": "Using javascript, in order to change what a user is viewing, what do you need to manipulate?",
            "answer": "DOM",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question": "What is 2 raised to 4?",
            "answer": "16",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question": "What is the most well known equation?",
            "answer": "E=MC^2",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "5",
            "question": "What is the most fundamental building block of matter?",
            "answer": "atom",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "6",
            "question": "Is programming fun?",
            "answer": "yes",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "7",
            "question": "How many chambers in a human heart?",
            "answer": "4",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "8",
            "question": "At what point in the cell cycle does crossover take place",
            "answer": "meiosis",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "9",
            "question": "How many nickels in a dollar?",
            "answer": "20",
            "pic": ""

        },
        {
            "id": "10",
            "question": "What is a meteor in the atmosphere called?",
            "answer": "meteorite",
            "pic": ""

        }
    ]
}